studybreaks.com 2008-12-12

# Privacy Policy :: StudyBreaks.com

Study Breaks, LP (“Study Breaks”) wants to make your experience as enjoyable and rewarding as possible by making sure you can use our vast array of information, tools, and opportunities with complete confidence. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

## What This Privacy Policy Covers

  * This policy covers how Study Breaks treats personal information that the company collects and receives on-line, including information related to your past use of Study Breaks products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This Privacy Policy covers all end users of Study Breaks’ services including those who access some of our services but do not have accounts (“Visitors”) as well as those who pay a monthly service fee to subscribe to the Study Breaks’ products or services (“Members”). 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Study Breaks does not own or to people that Pop Labs does not employ or manage, or to information that Study Breaks collects offline.

## Information Collection and Use

STUDY BREAKS collects information through our Web site when you contact us using our online contact form. We collect the following information about visitors when they register: First Name, Last Name, Gender, Birth Date, Bio, Network, School, Class, Interests, Website, Yahoo! ID, MSN/Live ID, Google ID, and AIM/ICQ ID.

  * Study Breaks collects personal information when you register with Study Breaks or when you use Study Breaks products or services, when you visit Study Breaks pages or the pages of certain Study Breaks partners, and when you enter promotions or contests sponsored by Study Breaks. Study Breaks may combine information about you that we have collected with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When you register we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, birth date, zip code and industry. Once you register with Study Breaks and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Study Breaks may collect information about your transactions with us and with our partners. 
  * Pop Labs automatically receives, records and tracks information about your visits to Study Breaks affiliated sites including IP address, visit duration, and the page you request. 
  * Study Breaks may use the information for at least the following general purposes: fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

  * Study Breaks may rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other nonaffiliated companies to provide products or services you may be interested in under the following circumstances:
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights, defend against legal claims, and satisfy the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, governmental or legal requests for such information. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Study Breaks’ terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
  * We believe it is necessary to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or other user policies. 
  * We transfer information about you if Study Breaks is acquired by or merged with another company. 
  * We provide the information to companies who work on behalf of or with Study Breaks. These companies may use your personal information to help Study Breaks communicate with you about offers from Study Breaks or other companies.

If you order products directly from the Study Breaks enrollment site, we will collect credit card data from you only to process that order or subscription. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

## Cookies

A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites.

  * Study Breaks may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks. 
  * Study Breaks cookies do not enable third parties to access any of your customer information.

## Web Beacons

A “Web Beacon” is a small string of code that provides a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. Study Breaks uses Web Beacons within to count users who have visited particular pages or to track certain paths through affiliated Web sites. Study Breaks uses Web Beacons in the following ways:

  * Study Breaks may include Web Beacons in HTML-formatted email messages (messages that include graphics) that Study Breaks, or its agents, send in order to determine which email messages were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon. 
  * Study Breaks uses Web Beacons on Study Breaks affiliated sites to track users and to analyze campaigns.

## Confidentiality and Security

  * We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 
  * We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

## Where to Direct Questions about Study Breaks Privacy Policy

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact our office: Study Breaks Magazine, Attn: Mail Dept, 2520 Longview St. Suite #315, Austin, TX 78705.

## Revisions to This Policy

Study Breaks reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms of Use and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner. Notice of any revision, amendment, or modification will be posted on Study Breaks web site.

### New to StudyBreaks.com?

#### For Students...

StudyBreaks.com is the place for college students like you to connect with all their friends, stay on top of all the best local artists and venues, find out about drink specials and special offers at their favorite bars, restaurants and clubs, and just take a break from studying.

#### For Venues...

We've got the students, you've got the fun. When you signup for an account on StudyBreaks.com, you get a free listing in our database with exposure to college students in your area. List your drink specials and special events. It's the easiest advertising you'll ever do.

#### For Performers...

Exposure is hard. StudyBreaks.com just made it a little easier. Promote yourself or your band to local college students for free. Create your profile, add a sample track, list upcoming shows. It's that simple.

Create Your FREE Account
